(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-03T22:59:35.756244",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ah whipしたケーキのような街は
Ah, a town like a whipped cream cake is...
好き！雪！本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real Magic!
空がくれるコンフェティは
The confetti falling from the sky is...
冬のフェスタ祝う天使の羽よ
like angel wings celebrating a winter festival!
本気マジック
Real Magic!
白銀の国へ
Off to the land of silver snow,
出かけるの Go Go Go
let's go, go, go!
雪の列車が
The snow train
街を駆け Choo Choo Choo
runs through town, choo choo choo!
絵本みたいな景色を君に見せてあげるから
I'll show you a picture-book view,
願い込めて
so make a wish
呪文さあ
and chant the spell,
唱えて
come on, sing along!
A B C D ドドシシララシシ
ABCD Do-Do-Ti-Ti-La-La-Ti-Ti
マジカル ミラクル クル Pop!
Magical, Miracle-kurukuru, Pop!
Ah whipしたケーキのような街は
Ah, a town like a whipped cream cake is...
好き！雪！本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real Magic!
空がくれるコンフェティは
The confetti falling from the sky is...
冬のフェスタ祝う天使の羽よ
like angel wings celebrating a winter festival!
Light upしたオーロラ色の街は
The lit-up aurora-colored town is...
好き！雪！本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real Magic!
子供でいられたら
If I could stay a child,
Dream Land
it'd be Dream Land!
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Melkiss!
ツンと冷たい
I love this crisp, chilly
季節が好き Love Love Love
season, love, love, love!
アイスも魔法も
Wishing the ice and magic
とけないように Hyuu Hyuu Hyuu
won't melt, whew, whew, whew!
ずっとこのままじゃダメなのは
We can't just stay like this forever,
やっぱりドキドキしたいな
because I still want to feel my heart race!
未来求め
Seeking the future,
呪文今
chant the spell now,
唱えて
come on, sing along!
1 2 3 4 水金地火木
1, 2, 3, 4, Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter!
マジカル ミラクル クル Pop!
Magical, Miracle-kurukuru, Pop!
Ah ホップしたウサギのような気分
Ah, feeling like a hopping rabbit!
好き！雪！本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real Magic!
大地がくれる
When I get energy
元気得たら
from the earth,
思い通り明日を生きていけるよ
I can live tomorrow just the way I want!
眩しい白に染まるハート君に
My heart dyed in dazzling white to you,
好き！雪！本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real Magic!
大人のふりなんて
Who cares about acting
いいじゃん
like an adult?
I hear that beat from town
The cute angel will come down
This is my home I'll let you know
Namara fantastic!
The snowscape is lyrical
The street gonna be magical
I'll set you free in my land oh oh oh
今日の寒さも忘れるように
So we can forget today's cold,
悩みだって悩みだって凍らせて
freeze all your worries, freeze them all away!
消せる魔法よ
It's magic to make them disappear!
A B C D ドドシシララシシ
ABCD Do-Do-Ti-Ti-La-La-Ti-Ti
マジカル ミラクル クル Pop!
Magical, Miracle-kurukuru, Pop!
Ah whipしたケーキのような街は
Ah, a town like a whipped cream cake is...
好き！雪！本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real Magic!
メルコンセプトは
Mel's concept is...
冬のフェスティバル 宴のハレよ
A winter festival, a grand celebration!
ライトアップした 七色の街は
Lit up in rainbow colors, the town...
好き雪 マジマジック
Love snow, real magic!
子供でいられたら
If only I could stay a child...
3 2 1 0
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
見てるー？ 見てるー？
Are you watching? Are you watching?
じゃん！ じゃんじゃん！
Ta-da! Ta-da, ta-da!
ちょこ先生のさっきのサンタ衣装と
Choco-sensei's Santa outfit from earlier...
メル様の雪だるま衣装
...and Mel-sama's snowman outfit...
交換してみましたー！
...we swapped them!
イエーイ！
Yay!
かわいいでしょー？
Cute, right?
どうかな？ どうかなー？
How is it? How is it?
めちゃめちゃ可愛くない？ この衣装！
Isn't this outfit super duper cute?
可愛いよねー！
It's so cute!
いっぱい写真撮って いっぱい曲の感想 ツイートしてほしいなー！
Take lots of photos and tweet lots of your thoughts on the songs!
このハッシュタグで！
With this hashtag!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
We appreciate it!
この後もね いっぱい楽しい曲が続くから
We have lots more fun songs coming up after this...
みんなもいっぱい声出して おうちでね サイリウムとか振って 楽しんでってね！
...so everyone, shout loud and wave your glow sticks at home, and have fun!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Thank you so much!
じゃあちょこ先生 早速次の曲 いきますか！ 行っちゃいますかー！
Now then, Choco-sensei, shall we move on to the next song right away? Shall we do it?
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
ハッとするような情景が
A breathtaking scene,
パッと消えそうな印象が
an impression that seems to vanish in a flash,
ぼくあたしのファインダーを満たしてキレイさ
fills our viewfinders and it's so beautiful.
どうでもいいけど
Not that it matters, though.
いいね！ いいね！ いいね！ いいね！
Like! Like! Like! Like!
パシャり キラリ フワリ もったり
Snap, sparkle, fluffy, soft,
背伸びナウ 天使ワールド
reaching high now, angel world.
不安定ジブン 愛して欲が
My unstable self desires to be loved,
「見せたい！」「見せたい！」 クレッシェンド
"I wanna show you! I wanna show you!" Crescendo.
流行り つまり 似たり 寄ったり
Trends, in short, all looking similar,
加工した 狭いワールド
an edited, narrow world.
飾んないキミを愛した熱も
Even the passion that loved the unadorned you,
「いらない！」「いらない！」 デクレッシェンド
"Don't need it! Don't need it!" Decrescendo.
味わう前に 口に出ちゃう ラブはインスタント
Expressing it before even tasting, love is instant.
キミのハートすら 欲しくなっちゃう 今日も
I even end up wanting your heart, today as well.
映えテクスタディ GO!
Photogenic tech study, GO!
ほう... こうやって可愛く加工すれば たくさん「いいね」もらえるのか...
Oho... So if I edit it cute like this, I can get lots of "likes"...
よーし！ ちょこも加工... どやあ！
Alright! Choco will edit it too... Ta-da!
あれ...？ やりすぎた...？
Huh...? Did I overdo it...?
いいね！ いいね！ 愛してみても
Like! Like! Even if you try to love it,
いいね？ いいね？ どうぞ お好きに
Like? Like? Go ahead, as you please.
いいね！ いいね！ 実は どうでも
Like! Like! Honestly, doesn't matter,
いいね！ いいね！ スキも キライも
Like! Like! Likes and dislikes both.
ハッとするような情景が
A breathtaking scene,
パッと消えそうな印象が
an impression that seems to vanish in a flash,
濁った日々のファインダーを
...blurring the viewfinder of murky days...
ぼかしてキレイだな
...and making it look pretty.
サッと繋がる感情も
Quickly connected emotions,
キミに届けた アイラブユーも
and the "I love you" sent to you,
ほんとはもっと 違っていたんだっけ？
were they actually different deep down?
どうでもいいけど
Not that it matters, though.
流行り？ ファッション？ イマイチ分からん！
Trends? Fashion? I don't really get it!
でもでもちょっと手を伸ばせ おしゃれ！
But reach out just a little, stylish!
あたしにだって 出来るはずなんだ！
I should be able to do it too!
まずは初の第一歩！
First, the very first step!
気軽に妄想 手軽に投稿
Casual fantasies, easy posts,
こんなあたしも いけてるエフェクト
even someone like me with a cool effect...
かけて登調したいの ヘヴン！
...wants to tune up and reach heaven!
思い立ったの 即登録！
Spurred to action, instant registration!
タグ付けする友達がいない！！
I have no friends to tag!!
位置情報？ あぁ 地図読めない！！
Location info? Ah, I can't read maps!!
これが SNSワールドの 洗礼 か
Is this the baptism of the SNS world?
必死にサバイブ ＆ エフォート
Desperately surviving & putting in effort,
あたしは ここだよ！ 見てくれ世間ッ
"I'm right here! Look at me, world!"
気になったなら 押して押されて say！ いいね！
If you're curious, press it, get pressed, say "Like!"
スキの音で 跳ねる衝動だけでいいやん
Just the impulse jumping at the sound of "like" is fine.
なんて思うのにさ
Even though I think that,
映える方向まで ついつい 追っちゃうよ
I end up chasing photogenic trends anyway.
ほう... こういう新しいものが「いいね」が稼げるのか...
Oho... So new things like this earn "likes", huh...
ならメルは この新作のふにゃペチーノを投稿！
Then Mel will post this new Funya-puccino!
あれ...？ これ中身こぼれてる... あちちっ！
Huh...? It's spilling out... Ouch, hot!
いいね いいね もっとくれたら
Like, like, if you give me more,
いいね いいね 不純だっていいよ
like, like, impure intentions are fine too.
インスタントな魔法で
With instant magic,
ぼくら ちょっと繋がれるんだ
we can connect just a little bit.
いいね！ いいね！ 愛してみても
Like! Like! Even if you try to love it,
いいね？ いいね？ どうぞ お好きに
Like? Like? Go ahead, as you please.
いいね！ いいね！ マジでどうでも
Like! Like! Seriously doesn't matter,
いいね！ いいね！ ラブの数 とか
Like! Like! The number of loves or whatever.
ハッとするような情景が
A breathtaking scene,
パッと消えそうな印象が
an impression that seems to vanish in a flash,
ぼくあたしのファインダーを満たしてキレイさ
fills our viewfinders and it's so beautiful.
どうでもいいことも追っかけ共有して
Chasing and sharing meaningless things too,
笑えた感情は“本当”なんだ！
the emotion of laughing was "real"!
だからもう映え映えとしたヘヴンなんて
So a picture-perfect heaven...
どうでもいいから
...doesn't matter anymore!
どうでもいいけど
It doesn't really matter, but
やっぱ撮っちゃう
I still end up taking photos of
派手なスイーツ
fancy, colorful sweets.
いいね いいね
Like it, like it!
キラリ光る 白い雪が
Shining bright, the white snow
少しずつ街を染めてゆく
gradually coats the town.
さあ 二人で奏でるメロディー
Come, the melody we play together...
探しに出かけよう
Let's go out and search for it.
この冬最後の雪が 僕らの街に舞い降りた
The last snow of this winter fell upon our town.
二人が歩いた道の 足跡消えてしまう
The footprints on the path we walked together are disappearing.
冷たい空気吸い込んで 泣き出しそうな空を見た
Breathing in the cold air, I looked up at the sky that seemed ready to cry.
明日の朝には二人 別々の場所へ歩き出す
Tomorrow morning, the two of us will set off for separate places.
臆病すぎた僕は 大事なことも言えず
Too cowardly, I couldn't even say what mattered most,
震える君のその手を 握ることさえも...
nor could I even hold your trembling hand...
キラリ光る 白い雪が
Shining bright, the white snow
少しずつ街を染めてゆく
gradually coats the town.
さあ 二人で奏でるメロディー
Come, the melody we play together...
探しに出かけよう
Let's go out and search for it.
長い夢が覚める前に
Before waking from this long dream,
この思い君に届けたい
I want to convey these feelings to you.
きっと また新しい歌声が
Surely, a new singing voice again
この空に舞い降りる
will flutter down upon this sky.
この冬最後の風が 僕らの街を吹き抜けた
The last wind of this winter blew through our town.
枯れ木に宿る蕾が 春の訪れを告げる
Buds resting on bare trees announce the arrival of spring.
おどけた顔で誤魔化して うつむく僕をからかった
Covering it up with playful faces, you teased me as I looked down.
去年の冬より少し 大人びた君のその笑顔
Your smile looked a little more mature than last winter.
不器用すぎた僕は 大事なこと見落とし
Far too clumsy, I overlooked what was truly important,
こぼれる君の涙に 気づくことさえも...
failing to even notice your falling tears...
出来なくて...
unable to do even that...
ヒラリ落ちる 白い雪が
Gently fluttering down, the white snow
少しずつ頬を染めてゆく
gradually colors my cheeks.
もう 二人で奏でるリズム
So that the rhythm we play together
途切れないように
won't ever be broken,
ずっと キラリ光る 白い雪が
forever, shining bright, the white snow
少しずつ空へ溶けてゆく
gradually melts into the sky.
ねえ 二人で奏でたメロディー
Hey, the melody we played together...
忘れはしないよ
I will never forget it.
長い夢が覚める頃に
Around the time this long dream wakes,
君はもう消えてしまうけど
you will already be gone, but...
きっと また懐かしい歌声が
Surely, a nostalgic singing voice again
新しい未来で
in a brand new future
光り輝く雪になって
will turn into shining, sparkling snow
この空に舞い降りる
and flutter down upon this sky.
...い降りる
...swooping down.
やがて 目の前に 舞い降りる
Finally swooping down right before me...
じゃあね、こっからは～
Now then, from here on out...
なんと！
Believe it or not...
撮影コーナーに入りまーす！
We're entering the photo corner!
やったー！
Yay!
てことで～
So with that...
ホロメンのね、何人かにちょっと来てもらって...
We're going to have some Holo members come over...
メルたちに取ってほしいポーズを指定してもらってですね...
and have them request poses they want us to take...
可愛いポーズをいっぱい撮りたいと思いますので...
So we can take lots of cute photos!
ちょっとね、着替えてきたいと思います！
We're going to go change real quick!
はい！ ちょっとだけね、待っててくださいね！
Yep! Please wait just a moment for us!
待っててね！
Wait for us, okay!
イエーイ！
Yay!
着替えてきたよー！
We changed!
みんなお待たせー！
Thanks for waiting, everyone!
メルサンタと～
Mel-Santa and...
チョコサンタでーす！
Choco-Santa!
イエーイ！
Yay!
じゃあね、早速1人目お呼びしたいと思います！
Alright then, let's call out our first guest right away!
はい！
Yes!
1人目は...この方！
The first guest is... this person!
キアラー！
Kiara!
キアラでーす！ メリークリスマス！
It's Kiara! Merry Christmas!
メリークリスマス！ キアラちゃん！
Merry Christmas! Kiara-chan!
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
ホーホーホー！ サンタクロースの2人ですか？ 可愛い！
Ho ho ho! Are you two Santas? So cute!
そうだよ！ だからチキン頂戴！
That's right! So give us some chicken!
そうよ、よこしなさい！ よこせ！
That's right, hand it over! Give it to us!
私不死鳥なんで、チキンはちょっと渡せないんですけども...
I'm a phoenix, so I can't really give you chicken, but...
ケチー！
Stingy!
海外のミームを真似してもらいたいなと思って来ましたけど...
I came because I wanted you two to recreate an overseas meme...
どうですかね？
What do you think?
ミーム？ いいよ！
Memes? Sure!
ミーム、そうそうそう。とある海外のアニメのポーズを真似してもらいたいです、2人で。
Memes, yes yes. I want you two to recreate a pose from a certain overseas anime.
オッケー！ 出来るかな？
Okay! Can we do it?
オッケーオッケー。そしたら、1人死にかけるようなキャラクターが必要なんですけど、死にかかけたい人誰ですか？
Okay, okay. So, we need one character who is on the verge of death. Who wants to be near death?
じゃあチョコ死にかかけます！
Then Choco will be near death!
イエーイ！ オッケーオッケー！
Yay! Okay, okay!
床に...えー、倒れてほしいです、まず。
First, I'd like you to... collapse on the floor.
バーン！ そうそうそう！
Bam! Right, right, right!
もうちょっと上向きですね。体、そうそうそう... いい感じ！
A bit more face-up. Body, right, right... Looking good!
で、そうしたら、メル先輩には、チョコ先生の隣に来てほしいんですけど...
And then, I want Mel-senpai to come next to Choco-sensei...
そうそうそう！ 可愛い可愛い！
Right, right! Cute, cute!
で、隣でしゃがんでほしいです。
And I want you to crouch next to her.
はい！
Okay!
そう、そんな感じ！ もうちょっと近くかな？
Yeah, like that! Maybe a bit closer?
YES, YES, YES!
YES, で、そこで... そうそう、「考えろ、チョコ！ 考えろ！」みたいなポーズを取ってほしい！
YES! And then... right, right, take a pose like "Think, Choco! Think!"
そういうことです！
Exactly!
もうバッチリです！
That's perfect!
セリフだけ言ってもらいたいな... あの、英語で。
I'd like you to say the line... in English.
"Think, Choco! Think!" って言ってほしい、怒った顔で。
I want you to say "Think, Choco! Think!" with an angry face.
オッケー！
Okay!
"Think, Choco! Think!"
ギャー！
Eek!
やばい！ これはね、Redditでいっぱい載せてもらえそう！
Awesome! This will definitely get posted a lot on Reddit!
アニメ「インビンシブル」！
The anime "Invincible"!
オッケー！ もう1個あるけど、もう1個の方はもうちょっと簡単だと思う！
Okay! There's one more, but I think the other one is a bit easier!
おー！ まず隣に立ってほしいです。
Ooh! First, I want you to stand next to each other.
はい！
Okay!
で、チョコ先生... 右腕をメル先輩の背中に載せてほしい。
And Choco-sensei... put your right arm on Mel-senpai's back.
そう！ で、左腕は...
Right! And your left arm...
なんか、メル先輩に何か遠いものを見せてるように... そうそうそうそう！
like you're showing Mel-senpai something far away... Yes, yes, yes, yes!
で、チョコ先生は嬉しい顔で、メル先輩は怖い顔で！ やばい！ みたいな！
And Choco-sensei with a happy face, and Mel-senpai with a scared face! Like "Oh no!"
泣いちゃう...
I'm gonna cry...
そうそうそうそう！ これね、とある映画の有名なミームでございます！
Yes, yes, yes, yes! This is a famous meme from a certain movie!
完璧！ 完璧！
Perfect! Perfect!
パチパチ！ ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
早速Redditで回します！ ありがとうございます！
I'll share this on Reddit right away! Thank you so much!
よろしくRedditー！ やったー、楽しー！
Please support it, Reddit! Yay, this was fun!
キアラちゃんありがとうー！ ありがとうございますー！
Kiara-chan, thank you! Thank you so much!
メリークリスマス！ メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas!
キアラちゃん、楽しかったねー！ ねー！
That was so fun with Kiara-chan! It sure was!
ありがとー
Thank you!
ということで、ふたり目はね、また衣装着替えようと思うので
So, we're going to change our outfits again for the second guest,
着替えてきたいと思います！
so we'll be right back after changing!
生着替えタイムでーす！
It's live outfit change time!
またねー！
See you soon!
じゃんじゃーん！
Ta-da!
着替えてきたよー
We're changed!
どうかなー？ 雪だるまメルと
How do we look? Snowman Mel and...
雪だるまチョコでーす！
Snowman Choco!
ということで、ふたり目早速呼んでいきましょう！
So, let's call out our second guest right away!
それじゃあ、ふたり目…
Alright then, guest number two...
もしもーし！
Hello?
はーい！
Yes!
もぐもぐー！おかゆー！おかゆちゃん！おかゆさまー！
Mogu mogu! Okayu! Okayu-chan! Okayu-sama!
メルちゃん、ヤッホー！遊びに来たよー
Mel-chan, yaho! I came to visit!
待ってたよー！
We've been waiting for you!
めっちゃさ、その雪だるま衣装めっちゃかわいい！
That snowman costume is super cute!
えー、ほんとにー？嬉しい！
Really? I'm so happy!
なんか雪だるまが1、2、3、4つぐらいついてる？
Are there like... 1, 2, 3, 4 snowmen on it?
ついてる、ついてる！
Yes, they're on there!
むつかもしれないけどね
Though there might be six!
6個ある、6個！
There are six, six!
1、2、3、4、5、6個だ！
1, 2, 3, 4, 5... There are six!
やったー！
Yay!
ふたりにさ、僕が指定したポーズをしてもらえるって聞いたんだけど
I heard I can get you two to do poses that I request?
そうなんだよー！何？何？
That's right! What is it? What is it?
なんかチョコ先生とメルちゃんだとNGがなさそうだよね
It feels like with Choco-sensei and Mel-chan, nothing is off-limits!
なんでもやっちゃうよー！任せてほしい！
We'll do anything! Leave it to us!
もしよっかな、やっぱちょっとくっついて可愛い、てぇてぇポーズをやってもらいたいから
Well then... since I want something cute with you two close together, a wholesome pose,
じゃあ、めっちゃぎゅーって近付いて、ふたりで…
how about getting super close together, hugging, and...
うわー！これはやばいです！
Whoa! This is amazing!
これはやばいですー！
This is incredible!
近付いてどうするのー？
We're close, so what should we do now?
ちょっと待って…やばいやばい！何？
Wait a second... Oh my gosh! What is this?
やばいよ、これ！
This is insane!
ちょっと正面向いてください！正面向いてください！
Please face forward! Face the front, please!
え、じゃあ正面向いて「にゃんにゃんポーズ」してください！
Okay then, face forward and do a cat pose!
はーい！
Okay!
にゃーん！
Meow!
待って、さっきの刺激が強すぎて声枯れちゃったよ！
Wait, that last moment was so intense my voice got raspy!
あーかわいい！おかゆ猫の仲間だにゃ！
Ah, so cute! You're fellow cats like Okayu now, meow!
可愛いー！じゃあチョコちゃんとメルちゃんのこと養ってくれるにゃ？
So cute~! Then will you take care of Choco-chan and Mel-chan, meow?
いいにゃー！2匹、2匹養ってあげるにゃーよ！
Sure thing, meow! I'll take care of both of you cats, meow!
嬉しいにゃー！
So happy, meow!
一緒に寝てくれるにゃ？
Will you sleep together with us, meow?
いいにゃーよ！何でも全肯定おかゆちゃん！
Sure thing, meow! I'm Okayu-chan who approves of everything!
いや、でもメルちゃんとチョコ先生を養うの、なんか荷が重そうだなー
Though, taking care of both Mel-chan and Choco-sensei sounds like quite a heavy burden~
えー！そんなに手間かかんないよ！
EH?! We don't take that much work!
確かにチョコ先生が荷が重そうやな
True, Choco-sensei does seem like a heavy responsibility.
チョコはちゃんと温めて寝かせてあげるわよ？
Choco will properly warm you up and tuck you in, you know?
ほんとにー？カイロカイロ！
Really? Like a body warmer!
チョコカイロ！
Choco body warmer!
え、どうしようかな？じゃあ次はー
Hmm, what should we do next? Then next...
後ろ向いてー
Turn around,
お尻フリフリとかどうですか？
and how about wiggling your butts?
お尻フリフリ！おかゆフリフリ！
Wiggling our butts! Wiggling for Okayu!
あ、ちょっとカメラマンさん際どいです！下げすぎ、下げすぎ！
Ah, cameraman, that angle is a bit risky! Too low, too low!
可愛いー！
Cute~!
じゃあ最後はー
Alright, for the last one...
こっち向いて、カメラに向かって投げキッスでお願いします！
Please turn around, face the camera, and blow a kiss!
はーい！
Okay!
おかゆ、大好きよ！
Okayu, I love you!
うわー！大好き！
Whoa! Love you!
うわー！超可愛いー！
Whoa! So cute!
やったー！ありがとう、おかゆちゃん！
Yay! Thank you, Okayu-chan!
ありがとう！限界です、さようなら…
Thank you! I've hit my limit, goodbye...
バイバーイ！またねー！
Bye-bye! See you later!
ありがとうー！にゃんにゃーん！
Thank you~! Meow meow~!
はぁ、おかゆさん、いつも通り癒されるねー
Ahh, Okayu-san is as soothing as always~
じゃあ最後の生着替え行きましょうか！
Well then, shall we go do our final live outfit change?
はい！行ってきまーす！
Yes! We'll be right back!
たったらーん！お待たせー！
Ta-da! Sorry to keep you waiting!
最後はやっぱりこの衣装だよね！
For the finale, it's gotta be this outfit!
まあまあ、私達アイドルですからね！
Well, well, after all, we are idols!
ということで…
So with that...
お邪魔しますか？
Excuse me.
誰なのかな...
I wonder who it is...
誰かな？もしもし！もしもし！
Who could it be? Hello? Hello?
はーい！
Yes!
こんラミ！
Kon-Lamy!
待ってた！待ってたよ！
We were waiting for you!
いやもうそのリボンちょっと可愛すぎやしませんか？
Aren't those ribbons just way too cute?
あ、そうなの？お揃い！可愛い！
Oh really? You two match! So cute!
めちゃめちゃ可愛い！もうお二人ともありがとうございます！
You're so super cute! Thank you both so much!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
え、なんか今日はもうラミィの好きなポーズを二人がとってくれるって聞いたんですけど。
So I heard the two of you would do Lamy's favorite poses today!
いや任せましたよ、プロデューサー！
We're leaving it to you, Producer!
プロデューサー！可愛い！
Producer! Cute!
え、じゃあ早速いいですか？早速いいですか？
Can we start right away?
はい！
Yes!
え、じゃあちょっと二人が向き合わせみたいな感じで、膝立ちで...
So, could you two face each other and kneel down?
座ってもらっていいですか？
Could you sit down?
あーそうそうそう！あーそうそう、あ、いいね、いいよいいよ！
Ah yes yes yes! Nice! Looking good!
で、ちょっとこう二人が抱き合う感じで。
And then have it look like you're hugging each other.
あーそうそうそうそう！
Ah, yes yes yes yes!
あ、からの、ちょこ先生ちょっとこっち向いて、あ、上目遣い！たまらん、あ、カメラマンさんいい！いいよ！
And then, Choco-sensei, turn over here... look up at the camera! Perfect! Cameraman, nice!
あ！いいね！いいね！可愛い！
Ah! Nice! So cute!
可愛い！
So cute!
そこでなんかドキドキメリークリスマスみたいな、なんかちょっと一言もらってもいいですか？
And then say something like "Exciting Merry Christmas"! Could you say a word?
近い！
So close!
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
メリークリスマス、メル様！大好き！
Merry Christmas, Mel-sama! Love you!
あー！ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Ah! Thank you so much! Thank you!
そしたらね、ちょっとすごく可愛い感じ... あーたまらん！
Next, give me a really cute... Ah, I love this!
えっと、立ってもらって...
Please stand up...
やっぱね、二人にちょっとこう下からもね、見たいので...
I also want to see you two from below, so...
下から？
From below?
近づいてもらって、二人にこう近づいてもらって、カメラマンさん下から！
Get closer, both of you get closer, and cameraman, shoot from below!
煽る感じで！あーいいねいいね！
Look down at us! Ah, nice, nice!
あ、いい！その煽り顔！煽り顔で！
Ah, that look! That looking-down face!
あー！いいね！
Ah! Nice!
かかってこいよ！あ、分かってきた！
Bring it on! I'm getting the hang of this!
かかってこいよ！
Bring it on!
あ、もっとこのちょっとギリギリを攻める感じにこうちょっと煽ってもらっていいですか？下からカメラマンさん！
Can you look down at us in a slightly risqué, edge-pushing way? Cameraman, lower!
もっと下ですね！はい、もうちょい下！もうちょい下！
Even lower! Yes, a bit lower!
あーちょっと...
Ah, wait...
あーもう大きいものでもうメル先輩の顔が見えない！
Ah, they're so big I can't even see Mel-senpai's face anymore!
ちょっと下から見たらブサイクになっちゃうでしょ！
Looking from below will make us look ugly, right?
あ、ごめんなさい！すみません！
Ah, I'm sorry! My bad!
ちょっと引いて... もうちょい下！もうちょい下！
Pull back a bit... Lower! Lower!
そうそうそう！もうちょい引いて！
Yes, yes, yes! Pull back a bit more!
あ！ダメ！ちょっと上！ちょっと上！ちょっと上！ちょっと上！
Ah! No! A bit higher! A bit higher!
メルのほうが身長小さいから、見えちゃう！
Mel is shorter, so it's going to show!
もうギリギリのところで脚を見せてもらう感じがいいんですけど、もうちょっと引きで見てもらったほうがいいですね！
I want to show off your legs right on the edge, but pulling back a bit more is better!
あ、そうですね！あ、そうそうそうそう！
Ah, yes! Yes, yes, yes, yes!
メル先輩、あぶないあぶない！そんな、お尻...
Mel-senpai, watch out! Don't show your butt!
お尻出しちゃダメ！そんな、ダメ！
You can't show your butt! No!
あー！もうダメ！
Ah! No way!
メル先輩！
Mel-senpai!
もう、ありがとうございます！そしたらもう、じゃあ飛び切りの...
Thank you so much! Next, with your best...
笑顔で、メリークリスマスと言ってもらってもいいですか？
...smile, could you say "Merry Christmas"?
はーい！
Sure!
ラミィちゃん、メリークリスマス！
Lamy-chan, Merry Christmas!
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
メリークリスマス！ありがとラミィ！
Merry Christmas! Thanks, Lamy!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
んー、まっ！
Mwah!
さあ、次の曲行こうかな？行っちゃおうかな？
Shall we move on to the next song? Let's go!
聴いて 愛する人の飛んでって
Listen to me, fly to the one I love
すこすこまるくらいに おねだり
Begging to be loved so very much
ねぇ ちゃんと聞いてみえ 受け取って
Hey, listen properly and accept it
甘く溶けちゃうような時間を
A time that melts softly and sweetly
疲れている顔して
With a tired face
いつもたくさん頑張ってるね
You're always working so hard
もう全て任せて
Leave everything to me
全部食べてあげようか
Shall I eat it all up for you?
よそ見なんて嫌だよ ちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
Don't look away, stay facing right here
目と目が合うでしょ 照れちゃうくらい見つめてね
Our eyes meet, right? Stare at me until you blush
愛しく 夢中にさせて
Make me fall endlessly in love
見つけてね
Find me, okay?
虜にしちゃうの
I'll make you fall for me
心拍数 急上昇
My heart rate is spiking fast
君に夢中 ズッキュン
Crazy about you, bang!
痛いの痛いの 飛んでけ
Pain, pain, fly away!
不安な顔より 笑顔見せて
Show me a smile instead of a worried face
ねぇ ちゃんと聞いてみて 受け取って
Hey, listen closely and take this in
甘いチョコのような時間を ここに
A sweet, chocolate-like time, right here
痛いの痛いの もう困っちゃう
Pain, pain, I'm at my wit's end
不意打ちにチョコアタック
An unexpected Choco Attack
焦らしちゃうわよ
I'm gonna tease you
ダメ もうちょっと
No, wait a little more
君の声をもっと 聞かせて
Let me hear your voice even more
不安なんて抱えて らしからぬなんて思ってた
Holding onto anxiety, thinking "this isn't like me"
全部全部 丸ごと包み込んで 溶かしてあげる
I'll wrap it all up and melt it away for you
みんなー！
Everyone~!
メルキス3周年ライブ、楽しんでるー？
Are you enjoying MelKiss's 3rd Anniversary Live?
もっともっとみんなと一緒にいたいから
Because I want to be with everyone more and more,
最後まで楽しんで 見ててね！
enjoy until the end and keep watching, okay?
どうしたって何したって 気持ちは同じなんだね
No matter what, no matter what we do, our feelings are the same
ここだってどこだって 思いは伝わるから
Whether here or anywhere, our feelings will reach, so...
声にして文字にして 勇気出して言って伝えよう
Put it into words, put it into text, gather your courage, and express it
今日だっていつだって 会いに行きたいの
Today and always, I want to go see you
愛してるの
I love you!
隠さないで ちゃんと教えて
Don't hide it, tell me properly
君のこと全部ちょうだい
Give me everything about you
聴いて 会いたいのに飛んでって
Listen, I want to see you so much I could fly to you
困るくらいにお願い
Please, so much that it's overwhelming
高鳴る心 聴いてみて 感じてほしいの
Listen to my throbbing heart, I want you to feel it
会いたいわ すぐ飛んでって
I want to see you, I'll fly to you right away
困るくらいにお願い
Please, so much that it's overwhelming
ねぇ ちゃんと聞いてみて 受け取って
Hey, listen closely and take this in
甘くとろけちゃうような時間を
A time so sweet it melts away,
隣にいたいから
Because I want to be by your side!
[曲名: 誇り高きアイドル]
[Song: Hokoritakaki Idol]
私のこと知ってますか？
Do you know who I am?
可愛く見えてますか？
Do I look cute to you?
私の歌どうだろうな
What do you think of my song?
うまく歌えてますか？
Am I singing well?
衣装だとかメイクだとか
My costume or my makeup,
可愛く見えてますか？
Do I look cute in them?
振付とかファンサとかも
My choreography and fan service,
喜んでもらえますか？
Do they make you happy?
手は冷たくなって
My hands are getting cold,
足は震える
My legs are shaking.
それでも戦いたい
Even so, I want to fight,
アイドルだから
Because I'm an idol!
バカにする奴は嫌いだ
I hate people who make fun of me,
見下されるのも嫌いだ
I hate being looked down upon too.
「アイドルなんか」という言葉を
Words like "just an idol",
見てもいないくせに言うな
Don't say them when you haven't even watched me!
頑張りを当然と言うな
Don't take my hard work for granted,
イメージとか強制するな
Don't force your image on me.
「アイドルなんか」という言葉は
Words like "just an idol",
この世で一番大嫌いだ
Are the ones I hate most in this world!
プライベート見えないから
Because you can't see my private life,
分からないと思います
I don't think you'd understand.
性格とか悪い方です
My personality is actually pretty bad.
騙しちゃっていますか？
Am I deceiving you?
でも本気です 本気なんです
But I'm serious, I really am!
ありのままの私を
Just the way I am,
好きになって 推してください
please love me and support me.
それってワガママですか？
Is that being selfish?
きっと可愛くない 全部分かってる
I'm probably not cute, I know all that.
それでも好かれてたい アイドルだから
But I still want to be loved, because I'm an idol.
皮肉言う奴は嫌いだ 言い訳ばかりも嫌いだ
I hate people who talk with sarcasm, and I hate constant excuses too.
こんなもんかという言葉を 軽々しく口にするな
Don't carelessly blurt out words like "Is that all you've got?"
勝手に限界を決めるな 笑いものになんてするな
Don't decide my limits on your own, and don't make a laughingstock out of me!
アイドルなんかという言葉は この世で一番大嫌いだ
I hate the phrase "just an idol" more than anything else in this world!
誇り高きアイドル
A proud idol!
目指そうぜ
Let me aim high!
声がなければ活動できない 好きなことばかりじゃ生きてはいけない
Without my voice, I can't perform. I can't live doing only what I like.
元気あげるはずが もらってばかりだし
I was supposed to give you energy, but I'm always receiving it.
恩返しできる日まで待ってて
Please wait until the day I can repay you!
歓声が減っても 飽きられちゃっても
Even if the cheers fade, even if people get tired of me,
それでも笑っていたい アイドルだから
I still want to keep smiling, because I'm an idol.
熱いファンの愛があって
With the passionate love of my fans,
スタッフさんの愛があって
with the love of the staff,
いつも家族の愛があって 生きてる
and with my family's constant love, I keep living.
アイドル！
Idol!
馬鹿にする奴は嫌いだ 見下されるのも嫌いだ
I hate people who make fun of me, and I hate being looked down on too.
アイドルなんかという言葉を 見てもいないくせに言うな
Don't say things like "just an idol" when you haven't even seen what I do!
頑張りは当然と言うな イメージとか強制するな
Don't take my effort for granted, and don't force your image on me!
アイドルなんかという言葉は この世で一番大嫌いだ
I hate the phrase "just an idol" more than anything else in this world!
放課後 二人で過ごした教室
In the classroom where we spent time together after school,
机の上 夢中ではずむ君の声
your voice bounces with excitement over the desks.
鈍感な君のその態度が
That oblivious attitude of yours
いつも私を 意地悪にさせるの
always makes me act mean toward you.
ひとりぼっちだと思う時もある
There are times when I feel all alone,
涙 止められない日もある
and days when I can't hold back my tears.
本当の私を見つめてほしいの
I want you to look at the real me.
きっと伝わると信じているよ
I believe that my feelings will surely reach you...
いるよ
I really do...
君はいつだって いつだって 変わらないから
Because you never, ever change,
私があの何度も 何度も シグナル送ってあげる
I'll send you signals time and time again.
夢見たあの丘 目指して
Aiming for that hill we dreamed of,
くじけそうな時も
even when I feel like giving up,
頑張れそうだよ
I feel like I can keep trying...
君がいるから
because you're here with me.
二人歩く いつもの帰り道
As we walk together on our usual way home,
名前のない 気持ちが芽生え始めてる
a nameless feeling is starting to sprout inside.
だけど踏み出すための勇気は
But the courage to take that step forward
少しだけ まだ遠くにある
is still just a little too far out of reach.
何も持っていなかった私に
To me, who had nothing at all,
君がくれた心の鍵は
the key to my heart that you gave me...
胸の奥で眠っていたつぼみに
To the buds slumbering deep within my chest
春の日差しを届けてくれる
delivers the warmth of spring sunlight.
君をいつだっていつだって想ってるから
Because I am always, always thinking of you,
きっとねいつの日かいつの日かちゃんとわかってほしい
surely, someday, I want you to truly understand.
二人で描いた未来を
So that we can gaze upon the future we drew together
もっと近い距離で見つめられるように
from a much closer distance,
夢見てるから
I am dreaming.
メル様～？これからもよろしくね！
Mel-sama~? Please continue to treat me well!
はあちゃま～！こちらこそ！
Haachama~! Likewise!
あの日触れた君のシグナル
The signal from you that I touched that day
始まりの扉が開くよ
opens the door to a new beginning.
あのね
You know,
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないでね
please don't ever, ever change.
私に何回も何回もシグナル送ってほしい
I want you to send me signals, time and time again.
輝くあの虹のように
Just like that shining rainbow,
涙のあとも奇跡に変えるよ
I will turn even the traces of tears into miracles.
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないから
Because you never, ever change,
私がいっつもいっつもシグナル送ってあげる
I will send you signals, time and time again.
夢見たあの丘目指して
Aiming for that hill we saw in our dreams,
くじけそうな時も頑張れそうだよ
even when I feel like giving up, I feel like I can do my best
君がいるから
because you are here.
イェーイ！
Yay!
ここまでいっぱい曲聴いてもらったけど、みんなどうだった？
We've performed a lot of songs so far, how did everyone like it?
どうだったかな～？
I wonder how it was~?
お～、ウケてる！
Oh, they love it!
え～、そんなによかった？めっちゃ嬉しい！
Eh, it was that good? I'm so happy!
メルもめっちゃ嬉しい！ありがとう！
Mel is super happy too! Thank you!
ありがとう～！
Thank you~!
でね、もうそろそろ終盤になってきたんだけど…
So, we're already getting close to the end...
え～、早～い！
Eh, so fast!
ここで、なんと重大発表です！
Right here, we have a major announcement!
イェーイ！
Yay!
なんと、なんと、メルキス3周年記念グッズが発売されます！
MelKiss 3rd anniversary commemorative merch will be released!
やった～！
Yay!
まず1つ目は…
First off, number one is...
コップ！私達とお揃いのメルキスコップが…
Cups! A MelKiss cup matching ours...
こちら！
Here it is!
かわいい～！
So cute~!
一緒にKPしよう！乾杯！
Let's cheers together! Cheers!
乾杯！そして2つ目は…
Cheers! And number two is...
こちら！
Here!
メルキスの可愛いロゴが入ったTシャツ！
A T-shirt with the cute MelKiss logo!
え、これ寝巻きとかにして着る？
Eh, should I wear this as sleepwear?
お出かけも一緒！黒と白があるよ～！
Wear it when going out too! It comes in black and white~!
いや～、もう2色ね、揃えちゃう？
Wow, two colors! Should we get both?
メルもお揃いにしちゃう～！
Mel will match too~!
ペアルック？
Matching look?
ペアルックもできるよ！
You can wear matching outfits too!
最高じゃん！
That's awesome!
そして、3つ目！
And, number three!
TAYA先生描き下ろしメルキスアクリルジオラマスタンド！
MelKiss acrylic diorama stand illustrated by TAYA-sensei!
イェーイ！
Yay!
めっちゃ可愛い！ヤバくない？
It's super cute! Isn't it amazing?
ヤバいよね！
It really is!
みんな見て！この立体感！
Everyone look! This 3D feel!
今回オリジナルで考えていただいたんですよ！
They specially came up with an original design for us!
めっちゃ可愛いでしょ！
Isn't it super cute!
メル達をお家にお迎えしてね！
Please welcome Mel and us into your home!
買っちゃうよね～！
You're definitely gonna buy it~!
さらに！
Furthermore!
今回は数量限定でメルキス2人の直筆サイン入りフルセットが販売されるよ！
This time, a limited-quantity full set with hand-written signatures from both of us in MelKiss will be sold!
ガチ？
For real?
ガチ！
For real!
ガチ～
For real~
しかも全部セットには メルキス撮り下ろしASMRボイスもついてくるよ！
And what's more, the full set comes with newly recorded MelKiss ASMR voice lines!
ななな なんだってー！？
Wh-wh-what did you say?!
イェーイ！
Yay!
な え？ 21時から...
Wh-eh? From 21:00...
うんうんうん 販売開始となるので なんと今から運営さんが概要欄にURLを貼ってくれます！
Yup yup yup. Sales begin then, so amazingly, starting right now, management will put the URL in the description box!
ワー！
Waaah!
ただーし！
How-ev-er!
このURL 21時からしか開けないので 皆様待機よろしくお願いしますね！
This URL won't open until 21:00, so everyone please wait patiently until then!
但し書よ！ 待機よろしくー！
There's a catch! Please wait patiently!
しかも この直筆サイン入りセット 数量限定だから早めにね！
Plus, this set with hand-signed autographs is limited in quantity, so get it early!
は 早めに！？
E-early?!
うん！ なくなっちゃったら メ達のサインもらえなくなっちゃうからね！
Yeah! If it sells out, you won't be able to get our autographs anymore!
な なんと！ なんということだー！
W-what! How could this be?!
お願いしまーす！
Please!
最後までドキドキ見るしかないじゃないかー！ この配信！
Then we have no choice but to watch this stream on the edge of our seats until the end!
どうぞよろしくお願いします！ / お願いしまーす！
Please look forward to it! / Please!
と いうことなんですけれども ちょこ先生？ / なに？
So, with that said... Choco-sensei? / What is it?
今日のこのライブ 何がコンセプトなんだっけ？
What was the concept for today's live stream again?
いやもう そんなの決まってるじゃない！ 私とメル様がイチャイチャするクリスマスライブよ！
Well, isn't that obvious?! It's a Christmas live where Mel-sama and I flirt with each other!
あ... うん そうなんだけど... それもそうなんだけど... もっと大事な... ほら Mel&Choco先生の...
Ah... well, yes, but... that's true too, but there's something even more important... See, for Mel & Choco-sensei...
ついにあの婚姻届に書いてくれることになった？
Did you finally decide to sign the marriage registration?
あー... 惜しいけど違うよ！ / 決意ができた？
Ah... close, but no! / Have you made up your mind?
惜しい！？ / 違う！
Close?! / No!
なになになになに！？
What, what, what, what?!
メルキスの3周年記念だよ！
It's MelKiss's 3rd Anniversary commemoration!
え？ もうちょこ達3周年経ったの？
Eh? It's already been 3 years for us?
そうだよ！ それにさ すごいことじゃない？
That's right! And isn't that amazing?
え ってことは... 3周年記念で... え こんな素敵なステージも用意してくれたの！？
Eh, that means... for the 3rd anniversary... you prepared such a wonderful stage for us?!
そうだよ！ / えー！ そう！
That's right! / Eh! Really!
ちょこ達 え クリスマス3周年ライブやりたいやりたいやりたいって言ってたから...
Because we kept saying we wanted to do a Christmas 3rd anniversary live...
うんうん 見て！ こちら！ / ね！
Yeah yeah, look! Over here! / Right!
なんと クリスマスツリー！ / クリスマスツリーにプレゼント！ / かわいい！
A Christmas tree! / A Christmas tree and presents! / Cute!
みんな気づいてた？ / 気づいてた？ 可愛いでしょう？
Did everyone notice? / Did you notice? It's cute, right?
そしてね 今回運営さんがね 色々準備してくれたということで ありがとうございます スタッフの皆様！ / ありがとうございます！
And management prepared various things for us this time, so thank you so much, staff members! / Thank you very much!
サンタ衣装もめっちゃ可愛かったよね！ / そう！
The Santa outfits were super cute too, right? / Right!
後でね みんな感想とかいろいろ待ってます！ / 待ってます！ ハッシュタグいっぱい呟いてね！ / トレンド入りさせろー！
We'll be waiting for everyone's thoughts and comments later! / Waiting! Tweet lots with the hashtag! / Make us trend!
ちょこ先生。 / 何？ / いつも優しくて... いつもメルのこと思ってくれて... たくさんメルに付き合ってくれる... ちょこ先生が メルは...
Choco-sensei. / What? / You're always so kind... always thinking of me... and hanging out with me so much... I... Choco-sensei...
大好き！
I love you!
そんな... ちょこもいつもメル様に頼ってばかりだけど... でもメル様といてすごく楽しくて...
No way... Choco always relies on Mel-sama too... but being with you is so much fun...
なんか... メル様とずっと一緒にいたいなって思うから... これからもよろしくね。
I feel like... I want to be with Mel-sama forever... So please treat me well from now on too.
こちらこそ これからもよろしく！
Same here, let me treat you well from now on too!
えーっと... ちょこ先生。 / 何？ / 大好き。
Um... Choco-sensei. / What? / I love you.
ちょ...
Cho...
ぎゃーーー！ そんなことされたら ちょこ心臓もたないよ〜！
Gyaaah! If you do that, my heart can't take it~!
いいですかー！？
Is it okay?!
もう一回しても... / もう一回？ 今度はちょこ先生がしてよ。 / ごめんごめんごめん！
Can we do it one more time... / One more time? This time Choco-sensei should do it. / Sorry, sorry, sorry!
ちょ ちょこ嬉しくて... 嬉しくてちょっとっぱいおねだりしちゃうかもしれないけど...
Ch-Choco is just so happy... I might end up asking for too much because I'm so happy...
メル様... / なん なんだい？
Mel-sama... / Wh-what is it?
ぎゃーーーー！
Gyaaaaah!
それ ちょこの挨拶... それちょこの挨拶取らないで... / 挨拶？ / ちょこの挨拶..."おはよう"って挨拶。
That's Choco's greeting... don't steal Choco's greeting... / Greeting? / Choco's greeting... the "Good morning" greeting.
おはよう みんな。 いろんな意味でおはよー！ / おはよう！
Good morning, everyone. Good morning in various ways! / Good morning!
と いうことで！ / はい。 / メルキスてぇてぇな感じで これからもメルキスをよろしくお願いします！ / よろしくお願いしまーす！
So with that said! / Yes. / With MelKiss being wholesome as always, please continue supporting MelKiss! / Please support us!
そしてね 残念なお知らせが1つ... / 残念なお知らせ？ / 次の曲で最後になります！
And also, we have one piece of sad news... / Sad news? / The next song will be our last!
ガチ？ / ガチ。
For real? / For real.
でも 嬉しいお知らせが1つ！ / うん。 / 次の曲 なんと... 重大発表の1つです！ / やったー！
But we also have one piece of happy news! / Mm. / The next song is actually... one of our major announcements! / Yay!
最後まで楽しんでってね！ / ちゃんと最後まで聴いてってね！ / それじゃあ...
Enjoy until the very end, okay! / Make sure to listen till the very end, okay! / Well then...
最後まで楽しもう！
Let's enjoy it until the very end!
行くわよ！ - うん！
Here we go! - Yeah!
Chu Chu Chu Chu 溶けそうで
Chu Chu Chu Chu, feeling like melting
Chu Chu Chu Chu 甘く欲しい
Chu Chu Chu Chu, wanting something sweet
Chu Chu Chu Chu 口づけを Choco Melty
Chu Chu Chu Chu, give me a kiss, Choco Melty!
よーし！行くぞー！
Alright! Let's go!
ほんの少しお疲れな平日に
On a slightly exhausting weekday,
幸せの箱開けちゃおう
let's open up a box of happiness!
甘い層の誘惑にも 乗ってみるの
Giving into sweet temptations too!
お疲れ様です！
Thank you for your hard work!
勝手気まま 強気な君のハート
Your willful, headstrong heart,
もっともっと好きになってね
fall in love with it more and more!
強がりだけど愛して
I pretend to be tough, but please love me!
寂しがらせないで ありがとう
Don't make me feel lonely, thank you!
メルキッスのオリジナル曲ができました！
MelKiss's original song is finally here!
ノリノリな曲だから いっぱい声出してね！
It's an upbeat song, so cheer real loud!
コールもあるから たくさん聴いて覚えるね！
There are chants too, so listen lots and learn them!
私たちと踊りましょう
Let's dance together!
今日も 明後日も
Today, and the day after tomorrow, too,
Merry Melty な恋となれ
may this be a Merry Melty kind of love!
焦がすキャラメル 召し上がれ
Enjoy this burnt caramel!
完璧なこの物語を
This perfect story...
ずっとついてきて
keep following us forever!
Sunny Lucky な日々を
These Sunny Lucky days,
君と見つめあう未来で
in a future where I gaze at you...
さあ よろしくね
Now, please be good to me!
Chu Chu Chu Chu 溶けそうで
Chu Chu Chu Chu, feeling like melting
Chu Chu Chu Chu 甘く欲しい
Chu Chu Chu Chu, wanting something sweet
Chu Chu Chu Chu ちょっと苦い 恋心 Melty
Chu Chu Chu Chu, a slightly bitter love, Melty!
よーし！行くぞー！
Alright! Let's go!
一息ついていいかな
Can I take a breath?
頑張りすぎも毒だし
Overworking yourself is toxic too,
誘惑も甘い誘惑も受け入れててね
please accept both temptation and sweet temptation!
ご苦労様です！
Great job out there!
見てあげるわ 君のハート
I'll keep an eye on your heart
ほの気取ってて 臭いかな？
Am I acting a bit too pretentiously, maybe?
私だけを愛して
Please love only me
寂しがらせないで
Don't make me feel lonely
え、なに？
Wait, what?
この曲で最後だって！？
This is the last song already?!
もう嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ！
No, no, no, no!
終わりたくないよ～！
I don't want it to end~!
私達とはしゃぎましょう
Let's party together!
いつも いつまでも
Always, and forever...
Merry Melty な恋かな？
Is this a Merry Melty kind of love?
チョコレートココアで召し上がれ
Enjoy it like chocolate cocoa!
イタズラなこのレシピを
This mischievous recipe...
もっとついてきて
keep up with us even more!
Happy Lucky な日々を
These Happy Lucky days,
終わりのないほど見つめて
gaze at them endlessly...
ずっと続くよ
It will go on forever!
ここにいれることが ただただ嬉しくて
Being here makes me so, so happy,
この大切な時間が 止まってほしくて
I wish this precious time would stop.
メルさんに出会えたこと
Meeting Mel-san,
ちょこさんに見つけてもらえたこと
being found by Choco-san...
甘くて甘い 最高な出会いを！
It's the sweetest, best encounter ever!
1. 両手広げて
1! Spread your arms wide,
2. 胸に抱きしめて
2! Hold it close to your chest,
3. 最後に笑顔で
3! Finally, with a smile,
わくわく キラキラ 届けて
deliver excitement and sparkles!
Reach して
Reach out!
もしもこの夢が 叶うとするのならば
If this dream were to come true...
幸せのカタチ作って
Shaping the form of happiness...
ビターでも シュガーでも
Whether it's bitter or sweet as sugar...
今日も 明後日も
Today, and the day after tomorrow, too,
Merry Melty な恋となれ
may this be a Merry Melty kind of love!
焦がすキャラメル 召し上がれ
Enjoy this burnt caramel!
完璧なこの物語を
This perfect story...
ずっとついてきて
keep following us forever!
Sunny Lucky な日々を
These Sunny Lucky days,
君と見つめあう未来で
in a future where I gaze at you...
さあ よろしくね
Now, please be good to me!
Chu Chu Chu Chu 溶けそうで
Chu Chu Chu Chu, feeling like melting
Chu Chu Chu Chu 甘く欲しい
Chu Chu Chu Chu, wanting something sweet
Chu Chu Chu Chu ちょっと苦い 愛心
Chu Chu Chu Chu, a slightly bitter heart filled with love
Chu Chu Chu Chu メロメロで
Chu Chu Chu Chu, completely head over heels
Chu Chu Chu Chu 刺激的
Chu Chu Chu Chu, so stimulating
Chu Chu Chu Chu 口づけを Choco Melty
Chu Chu Chu Chu, give me a kiss, Choco Melty!
よーし！行くぞー！
Alright! Let's go!
メルキス 3周年 LIVE Xmas Party
[MelKiss 3rd Anniversary LIVE Xmas Party]